Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/2
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Employes' Suggestion System Operating Manual, Publication (Box 24, Folder 25)
    February 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Illinois Central Magazine, Publication (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: An Opportunity to be Heard, Publication (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Labor-Management Relations in the Illinois State Service, Publication (Box 24, Folder 26)
    By Richard C. McFadden. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Local Human Relations Commissions And Councils In Illinois, Publication (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: '68 a bright year for a career in Illinois government, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Rules, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
    October 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Personnel Code, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
    August 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Rules, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
    November 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Personnel Code, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: The Personnel Code, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Rules, Publication (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Special Message On Collective Negotiations For Public Employees From Governor Otto Kerner To 75th General Assembly, Publication (Box 24, Folder 29)
    By Otto Kerner. May 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Reporter, Publication (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Friends, Publication (Box 24, Folder 30)
    January 8. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Careers In Retailing Week Chairman's Handbook, Publication (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Rules And Regulations for administration of The Illinois Unemployment Compensation Act, Publication (Box 24, Folder 32)
    July 7. Item is in English.
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: State Employees' Retirement System, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
    September 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Text Of The Act relating to State Employees' Retirement System, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
    By Adlai E. Stevenson. August 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Handbook of Information, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Handbook Of Information, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: State of Illinois Information Regarding Amendments To State Employees' Retirement System Act, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
    August 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Standard Policy, Publication (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Box: 24, folder: (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: A Brochure Prepared Especially for Country Superintendents Assistant County Superintendents Administrators, Publication (Box 24, Folder 34)
    September 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Dirt on California Agribusiness And The University, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Why Supplemental Unemployment Benefits Are Not Permissible Under Illinois Law, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    December 20. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Civil Service Handbook, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Holders of Policy and Rules -- Nonacademic, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    October 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Policy And Rules-Nonacademic, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    June 30. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Faculty Handbook 1968-69, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: University of Illinois Division of University Extension Presents An Educational Institute for the Illinois Chapter of the International Association of Personnel in Employment Security, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    October 30- November 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations annual report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Welcome to Illinois, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: This Is Your Civil Service Handbook For 1962-1963, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 15th Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    July 1-June 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: This is your Civil Service Handbook for 1965-1967, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: I.C.I. Memoranum On Labour Relations, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Independent Lock Company and the Hardware Employees' Association, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Talent Scouts for Leadership, Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
    By Diantha DeGraw. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Occupational Facts, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Compilation Of Official Rules, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    August 17. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Personnel 1959 Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employment Policies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
    September. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: faculty handbook, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Adviser Corps, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    January 1-September 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Accident Prevention, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Industrial Health Council of Greater Atlanta, Publication (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: 1953 Industrial Health Conference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 18)
    April 18-25. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Publications List, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: 1966 Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Third Quarterly Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Industrial Hygiene Foundation Activities, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Minutes of Annual Membership Meeting and Summary of 1961 Activities, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
    October 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Twenty-Seventh Annual Membership Meeting and Summary of 1962 Activities, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
    October 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial Hygiene Foundation 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Suggested Principles And Procedures For Developing Data For Threshold Limit Values For Air Experimental Animal Data Data from Human Subjects, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Current Federal Workmen's Compensation And Health And Safety Legislation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Employee Mental Health And Industrial Nursing Practices A Pilot Study of Current Practices, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Membership Information, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Industrial Hygiene Foundation Activities, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: History of Industrial Hygiene Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Nineteenth Annual Meeting Industrial Hygiene Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
    November 17-18. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Eighteenth Annual Meeting Industrial Hygiene Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
    November 18-19. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Industrial Hygiene Foundation 1951 Memo To Members, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: General Meeting, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
    November 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Industrial Hygiene Foundation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Labor-Saving Management, Publication (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1952 Industrial Management Council of Rochester, Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Industrial Management Council of Rochester Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Industrial Management Council of Rochester Annual Report 1953, Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: 40th Anniversary Industrial Management Council of Rochester Annual Report 1956, Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Industrial Management Council of Rochester Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Association of Buffalo, Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Association of Buffalo, Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Nineteenth Annual Midwest Conference On Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
    May 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Membership List, Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: "America's Decade of Decision" at the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
    By John Lyon Collyer. May 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Proceedings Of A Conference Commemorating The Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
    May 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Our First Twenty-Five Years 1926-1951, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Guest List, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Dear Mr. Naas, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
    May 14. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Past Publications, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: The IRRA invites you to become a member, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Statement From The Committee On Elections, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Statement From The Committee On Elections, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Program Annual Spring Meeting, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    April 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: You are invited to become a member of The Industrial Relations Research Association, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Industrial Relations Research Association Series, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Industrial Relations Research Association Series, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Marketplace For Understanding, Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: An Adventure in Multiple Management, Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
    February 10. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: An Adventure in Multiple Management, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: West Virginia Reports Progress, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Council In Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Labor Day 1955 Statement of Social Action Department National Catholic Welfare Conference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: The Just Price And The Legal Just Price, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
    By William G. Atkinson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Industry Council Plan And the State, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
    By John P. Walsh. February. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Voluntary Procedures and Processes in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
    By Irving M. Ives. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Conflict or Cooperation?, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
    By Thomas P. Manning. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Teamwork for---, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Inland Steel Company Annual Report Design for the Seventies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Employee Information Survey, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1955 Inland Steel Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Inland Steel Company Annual Report Design for the Seventies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Inland Steel Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Inland Steel Company 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: inland now, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: Inland Steel Company Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 9: Inland Steel's chicagoland operations, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 10: A Report from Inland Steel Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 11: Personal Recordings, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 12: Bubble Puffers, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 13: Haywire Hustleres, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 14: Explaining What To Whom?, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    June 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Benefit Performance, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 16: Right Angle Views, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 17: To All Employees:, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    November 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: To All Indland Men And Women, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    January 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Twin City To Hist Overtime Parking, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    April 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Production High Despite Floods, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 21: Sales Forecast: Cloudy, But Fair for the Year, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    June. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Inland The Magazine of the Middle West, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    Spring. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Milcor News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 24: Inland Steel Company 1965 Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 25: Inland News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    November 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Inland News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 27: Inland The Magazine of the Middle West, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    Summer. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Annual Report 1959 Inland Steel Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 29: Wheelwritght News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 30: Description of the Principal Provisions of The Pension Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: A Guide To Selection OF Applicants For Employment, Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Industrial Relations Poilcy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
    September 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Opportunitites At Inland, Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Attitudes Toward Retirement, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Inland Steel-Ryerson Scholarships, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Inland Steel Indiana Harbor Works Scholarships, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: On The Job Medical Services Available To General Office Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: Protection For You and Your Family, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 9: Questions And Answers about the Inland Steel Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: Setting Sails For Security, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 11: Inland Steel Company Shares Of Capital Stock Without Par Value Covered by Inland Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
    June 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: To All Employees Newly Eligible For The Inland Stock Purchase Plan:, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
    December 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Inland Major Meidcal Expense Group Insurance, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 14: Questions And Answers about the Inland Steel Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations Policy, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 16: Investments held By The First National Bank of Chicago as Trustee of the Inland Steel Company Pension Trust and Past Service Pension Trust (Combined Report), Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
    December 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 18: Pension Agreement With Description Of Principal Provisions, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 19: Program of Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: employeee suggestion plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: The Inland Steelmaker, Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
    February 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Inland Steelmaker, Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
    May 13. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: 1959 Proposals submitted to the United Steelworkers of America on June 22 1959 by the Negotiators for the Twelve Coordinating Companies, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Facts About the Steel Strike, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
    By Edward L. Ryerson. October 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Facts About The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 4: Facts About The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
    By Edward L. Ryerson. October 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Do You Know What The Steel Strike Is About?, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 6: Does anyone know what the Steel Strike is about?, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 7: Facts About The Steel Strike, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 8: The Industrial Relations Committee Of The Inland Steel Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Grab your coat and get your hatJust direct your feetTo the "Inland" side of the street!, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Clarence B. Randall, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: William G. Caples, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: Administration Department, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: Holding its own against the titans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    December 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Inland Steel Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    By T.J. Ess. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Steel's Progress And Problems, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    By Joseph L. Block. September 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Grab your coat and get your hatJust direct your feelTo the "Inland" side of the street!, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 9: The Inland Steel Building, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 10: The Age of Steel, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 11: "Industiral Peace", Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    By Nathan Shefferman. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Steel, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 13: Inland Officers Report to Stockholders at Annual Meeting April 25, 1956, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    April 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Steel Industry's Greatest Challenge, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    By Joseph L. Block. October 16. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Highlights of Pension Plan For Employees Of Ingersoll-Rand, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
    September 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees' Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Management Opportunities At Iland Steel Indiana Harbor Works, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: Management Opportunitities At Inland Steel, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 5: Salaried Recruitment 1959 Annual Report, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: High School Recruitment Annual Report 1958-1959 Indiana Harbor Works Inland, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 7: Employees' Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 8: Career Opportunities For High School Graduates 1960, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 9: Your Job with Inland, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 10: School Reference, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Highlights of the New Local 313 IUE-CIO and Ingersoll-Rand Co. Contract, Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
    August 28. Item is in English.
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Our latchstring is out, Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Box: 25, folder: (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: U.S. Navy LST. 1165 Launched, Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
    July 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ingalls' Expanding Production Is Being Met By Housing, Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
    March 13. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Institute of Collective Bargaining & Group Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: For Release Thursday A.M., Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    March 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Collective bargaining Institute, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: General, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    April 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: For Release 1:00 P.M., Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    April 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: General, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Catalog of Teaching Aids On Life And Health Insurance And Money Management, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Life Insurance News Data, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    July 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Life Insurance News Data, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    August 18. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Life Insurance Fact Book, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Family Economist, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    April 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Life Insurance News Data, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Life Insurance News Data, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    May 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Family Economist, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    June 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Family Economist, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Catalog of Teaching Aids On Life And Health Insurance And Money Management, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Catalog Of Teaching Aids On Life And Health Insurance And Money Management, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: You Are Important, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: A Catalog of Informational Materials on Life Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Box: 26, folder: (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Who is the man who sells life insurance?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: invitation to youth, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A Career For You In A Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)